export const data = {
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "How would you describe your thoughts when facing challenges or distressing situations?",
            "options": [
                "Calm and composed",
                "Occasionally uneasy",
                "Frequently consider self-harm",
                "Consistently experiencing urges for self-harm"
            ],
            "correctOption": "Consistently experiencing urges for self-harm"
        },
        {
            "question": "How often do you find yourself contemplating self-harm as a coping mechanism?",
            "options": [
                "Rarely or never",
                "Occasionally",
                "Frequently",
                "Regularly, leading to persistent thoughts of self-harm"
            ],
            "correctOption": "Regularly, leading to persistent thoughts of self-harm"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you often feel overwhelmed by emotions that drive you towards self-harming behaviors?",
            "options": [
                "Never",
                "Rarely",
                "Sometimes",
                "Frequently"
            ],
            "correctOption": "Frequently"
        },
        {
            "question": "How long do episodes of considering or engaging in self-harm typically last?",
            "options": [
                "A few minutes",
                "Several minutes",
                "Half an hour or more",
                "Varies, leading to persistent self-harming behaviors"
            ],
            "correctOption": "Varies, leading to persistent self-harming behaviors"
        },
        {
            "question": "Have you sought professional help or been diagnosed with self-harm or self-injury issues?",
            "options": [
                "Yes",
                "Considering it",
                "No, not yet",
                "No, and I don't plan to"
            ],
            "correctOption": "Considering it"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do these experiences of self-harm impact your daily life, relationships, or activities?",
            "options": [
                "Low impact",
                "Moderate impact",
                "High impact",
                "Very high impact"
            ],
            "correctOption": "Very high impact"
        },
        {
            "question": "Have others expressed concern about your experiences of persistent thoughts of self-harm or self-harming behaviors?",
            "options": [
                "Never",
                "Rarely",
                "Sometimes",
                "Frequently"
            ],
            "correctOption": "Frequently"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you believe that addressing and managing self-harming behaviors is important for overall well-being?",
            "options": [
                "Strongly agree",
                "Agree",
                "Neutral",
                "Disagree"
            ],
            "correctOption": "Strongly agree"
        },
        {
            "question": "How long have you been experiencing persistent thoughts of self-harm or engaging in self-harming behaviors?",
            "options": [
                "A short period",
                "Several months",
                "Years",
                "I haven't experienced persistent thoughts of self-harm or engaged in self-harming behaviors"
            ],
            "correctOption": "Years"
        },
        {
            "question": "Have you noticed changes in your sleeping patterns, such as difficulty falling asleep, staying asleep, or experiencing excessive sleepiness?",
            "options": [
                "Occasionally",
                "Frequently",
                "Consistently",
                "I haven't noticed any changes in my sleeping patterns"
            ],
            "correctOption": "Consistently"
        }
    ]
}
